{
    "data": {
        "title": "Vulgar Coffee Trivia",
        "cards": [
            {
              "question": "What is a Coffee Shop chain that starts with an 'S'?",
              "hint": "It rhymes with barlucks.",
              "answer": "Starbucks, its boss."  
            },
            {
                "question": "What is a Chemex?",
                "hint": "besides stupid and pretentious",
                "answer": "A shitty way to take too long to make coffee."  
              },
              {
                "question": "What is used to turn coffee beans into coffee grounds?",
                "hint": "You should know this, its pretty much in the question.",
                "answer": "A coffee Grinder, dipshit."  
              },
              {
                "question": "What do coffee, crack, pcp, meth and heroin have in common?",
                "hint": "I think we can all agree...",
                "answer": "THEY'RE FUCKING GREAT!"  
              },
              {
                  "question": "What is the douchiest way to make coffee?",
                  "hint": "its what assholes with too much time do.",
                  "answer": "pour-over"  
                },
                {
                  "question": "Where is the best coffee from?",
                  "hint": "El Salvador is a good guess",
                  "answer": "El Salvador"  
                },
                {
                    "question": "How do you make coffee beans?",
                    "hint": "Think really hard",
                    "answer": "You grow them ya dumb fuck."  
                  },
                  {
                      "question": "Who should not be allowed coffee?",
                      "hint": "...",
                      "answer": "Assholes, dipshits, douchebags, and fuckers."  
                    },
                    {
                      "question": "Why is coffee prohibited in Gallup New Mexico?",
                      "hint": "just try",
                      "answer": "It's not, ya bitch."  
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "What is the stupidest thing in the world?",
                        "hint": "it has to do with coffee.",
                        "answer": "Decaf coffee, fuck that."  
                      }
        ]
    }
}